because after words said in his last
porque tras palabras dichas en su último
Stream people suspect that Gemita would have
Stream la gente sospecha que gemita lo
cheated on him again It is evident that
habría vuelto a engañar Es evidente que
Auron was trying to get back with
auron estaba intentando volver con
Gemita that is why the Kim thing It is that with
gemita por eso lo de la Kim Es que de
so many lies I already eat them all you I
tanta mentira Ya me las como todas tú me
eat them all you I put this on
las como todas tú esto lo puse yo en
Twitter what did he do as the joke not that he
Twitter que hizo como la broma no de que
ate the Ricky issue No
se comió el tema de Ricky No el bite
this bite that Ricky did not with a
este que hizo Ricky no con lo de un
false event well I have eaten
evento falso pues me he comido también
Ricky's too edit It is not It is that no no I do not
la de Ricky edit No es Es que no no no
learn you of course I understood it as a
aprendo tú claro Yo lo entendí como una
joke because of his thing with Gemita not because
broma por lo suyo con gemita no por lo
of Cook and others I did not take it for granted that it was
de Cook y demás no di por heo que se
something current I do not learn you it is
tratase de algo actual no aprendo tú es
an incredible thing you are that I eat
una cosa increíble tú es que me me me
even the one of He is even cheating on me Ricky
como hasta la de Hasta me engaña Ricky
edit you this already what the [ __ ] is this This is
edit tú esto ya qué es esto Esto es
a wonderful thing you already cheated on me
una cosa maravillosa ya me engañaste a
Ricky edit you Auron and Gemita are not
Ricky edit tú auron y gemita no están
together but they have not broken up their relationship
juntos pero tampoco han roto su relación
because they never gave each other a second
porque jamás se dieron una segunda
chance officially It is that what
oportunidad de forma oficial Es que lo
happens is that they saw each other again they
que pasa es que ellos Se volvieron a ver
would be hooking up they would throw whatever
se estarían liando echarían lo que fuera
not what is appraised and they never returned of
no lo que se tase y nunca volvieron
course
claro